const qBank = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "Dee walks into Paddy's Pub and announces to the gang that she got a part in a movie. Who is the director?",
    options: ["James Cameron", "M. Night Shyamalan", "Guillermo Del Toro", "Quentin Tarantino"],
    answer: "M. Night Shyamalan",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "What’s the only infraction Paddy’s Pub receives on its health inspection in 'Charlie Work'?",
    options: ["Clogged toilet in men’s room", "Carbon monoxide leak in basement", "Wet drainage pipes", "Dumpster too close to door"],
    answer: "Dumpster too close to door",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which 'Sunny' character does Dennis hit with his car, halting the gang's trip to the strip club?",
    options: ["Charlie", "Dee", "Mac", "Frank"],
    answer: "Charlie",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is the name of Mac's dog?",
    options: ["Spot", "Rascal", "Poppins", "Rocket"],
    answer: "Poppins",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Dee goes out for a night on the town with the Waitress and Artemis. Which TV show is she trying to create?",
    options: ["Desperate Housewives", "The Golden Girls", "Sex & the City", "Army Wives"],
    answer: "Sex & the City",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which one of the characters is not in season 1?",
    options: ["Charlie", "Dee", "Mac", "Frank"],
    answer: "Frank",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "When Charlie and Frank work as a team, what do they call themselves?",
    options: ["The Renaissance Men", "The Gruesome Twosome", "The Nightcrawlers", "The Partners in Crime"],
    answer: "The Gruesome Twosome",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "What is the alias that Dennis comes up with for Charlie, when he and Mac are entering him into the underground fight tournament?",
    options: ["Day Man", "Hundred Dollar Baby", "Clown Baby", "Ghoul Baby"],
    answer: "Clown Baby",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "What artist are Dennis and Dee listening to on the porch in the episode 'The Gang Goes on Welfare'?",
    options: ["Sir Mixalot", "Too Short", "Notorious B.I.G", "Biz Markie"],
    answer: "Biz Markie",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which film director portrays Pappy McPoyle, the clan’s patriarch?",
    options: ["James Cameron", "M. Night Shyamalan", "Guillermo Del Toro", "Quentin Tarantino"],
    answer: "Guillermo Del Toro",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "In 'Charlie Kelly: King of the Rats,' which item was NOT drawn in Charlie’s dream journal?",
    options: ["Rat stick", "Worm hat", "Denim Chicken", "Bird with teeth"],
    answer: "Rat stick",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "How many cans of beer in total were drunk in 'The Gang Beats Wade Boggs'?",
    options: ["212", "182", "165", "158"],
    answer: "182",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "In 'Thundergun Express,' the gang recites the movie’s tagline: 'No hesitation! No surrender! No man left behind!' Name the members of the gang in order as they are left behind.",
    options: ["Dee, Charlie, Frank, Mac", "Dennis, Frank, Mac, Dee", "Charlie, Frank, Dee, Dennis", "Mac, Dennis, Dee, Charlie"],
    answer: "Dennis, Frank, Mac, Dee",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Which Quentin Tarantino film is parodied at the end of 'Charlie Catches a Leprechaun'?",
    options: ["Reservoir Dogs", "Pulp Fiction", "Kill Bill", "Django Unchained"],
    answer: "Reservoir Dogs",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "What is NOT an ingredient in Fight Milk?",
    options: ["Eggs", "Vodka", "Milk", "Sugar"],
    answer: "Sugar",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      "What’s the name of the psychiatric hospital that issued Frank a certificate declaring he doesn’t have 'donkey brains'?",
    options: ["Schuylkill State Institution", "State Hospital of Philadelphia", "Zimmer Mental Hospital", "Reid Mental Institution"],
    answer: "Reid Mental Institution",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "When Charlie eats a pear for the first time in 'The Gang Hits the Road,' what does he say it tastes like?",
    options: ["Chalk", "Paint", "Sand", "Glue"],
    answer: "Sand",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "What is Mac's real name?",
    options: ["Reggie", "Ronald", "Randy", "Ross"],
    answer: "Ronald",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "What type of law is Charlie educated in?",
    options: ["Bird Law", "Aviary Law", "Fowl Law", "Crow Law"],
    answer: "Bird Law",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Charlie admits that they crashed Nickie Potnick's car in high school. What did they crash the car into?",
    options: ["a car", "a cyclist", "a tree", "a traffic sign"],
    answer: "a tree",
  },
];

export default qBank;
